listango.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Listango

###  Fundamental Principles 

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. 
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights. 
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services. 
  * We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, kept private, and permanently deleted. 

If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our [support team.](mailto:support@listango.com) Listango, LLC (“Listango”) operates the website Listango.com. It is Listango’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. 

###  Website Visitors 

Like most website operators, Listango collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Listango’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Listango’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Listango may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

Listango also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. Listango only discloses logged in user addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below. 

###  Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information 

Certain visitors to our website choose to interact with Listango in ways that require Listango to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Listango gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with Listango are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Listango collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Listango. Listango does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

###  Aggregated Statistics 

Listango may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. For instance, Listango may monitor the most popular bookmarks on the Listango.com site. Listango may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Listango does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

###  Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information 

Listango discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Listango’s behalf or to provide services available at our website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using our website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Listango will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Listango discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Listango believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Listango, third parties or the public at large. 

If you are a registered user of the Listango.com site and have supplied your email address, Listango may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or keep you up to date with what’s going on with Listango and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Listango takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

###  Cookies 

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Listango uses cookies to help Listango identify and track visitors, their usage of our website, and their website access preferences. Listango visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using our website, with the drawback that certain features of our website may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

###  Business Transfers 

If Listango, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Listango goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Listango may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

###  Ads 

Ads appearing on our website may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Listango and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

###  Privacy Policy Changes 

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Listango may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Listango’s sole discretion. Listango encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
